Guide to the Chick Tract Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
Chick Tract Collection
1961-2015
RG 270
Yale University Divinity School Library
2
(4 boxes)
Controversial tracts written and illustrated in comic book format by Jack T. Chick since the early 1960s document a fringe element of American Christian fundamentalism and provide valuable insight into the reaction of evangelicalism to cultural upheavals in America society.
Chick, Jack T., 1924-2016
Biographical / Historical
Jack Thomas Chick was born April 13, 1924, in Boyle Heights, California. Following his graduation from high school, he studied acting at the Pasadena Playhouse School of Theater but was drafted into the U.S. Army in 1943 and served for three years in New Guinea, Australia, the Philippines, and Japan.
After the war, Chick returned to his studies at the Pasadena Playhouse and there met his future wife there, Lola Lynn Priddle. Priddle came from a religious background and introduced Chick to evangelical religion, including the Old Fashioned Revival Hour radio show, which Chick indicates was instrumental in his conversion.
Eager to share his religious faith but anxious about verbal interactions with people, Chick came up with the idea of using his artistic talents to create tracts that could be given to people directly or indirectly. He self-published his first tract, "Why No Revival?," in 1960 and published his second tract, "A Demon's Nightmare," in 1962. By 1970 Chick Publications was officially established in Rancho Cucamonga, California. Chick wrote and illustrated all of the comics himself, until 1972 when he hired another artist, Fred Carter, to illustrate many of them. The tracts attracted a large following though Christian bookstores were reluctant to stock them, due to their controversial nature.
For more biographical information about Jack Chick, see his website: https://www.chick.com/information/authors/chick.asp.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired by anonymous donation and purchase, 2015
Scope and Contents
The controversial tracts written and illustrated by Jack T. Chick since the early 1960s document a fringe element of American Christian fundamentalism and provide valuable insight into the reaction of evangelicalism to cultural upheavals in America society. Chick has printed and distributed more 800 million Christian fundamentalist tracts, which have been translated into more than 100 languages. The tracts are of a distinctive comic book format, three inches high by five inches wide in dimension, and usually 24 pages in length. The front panel features the title of the tract and the inside back panel is devoted to a standard sinner's prayer. While many of the tracts convey theological views generally accepted in evangelical Christian thought, a substantive number express more controversial ideas, attacking evolution, homosexuality, paganism, witchcraft, Catholicism, rock music, role-playing games, and other aspects of American popular culture. Chick is particularly known for his attacks on Roman Catholics, Freemasons, Muslims, and Jews.
As noted by Cynthia Burack, author of the article "From Doom Town to Sin City: Chick Tracts and Anti-gay Political Rhetoric" (New Political Science. June 2006): "Some Christian Right opinion leaders regard the tracts with ambivalence, and many outside the Christian conservative community who comment on Chick's career believe that the tracts are no longer available through Christian retail outlets. Not only are the tracts still available, they represent an important form of conservative Christian political pedagogy." For more information about the development and impact of Chick tracts, see the article on Chick in the reference work Culture Wars in America: an Encyclopedia of Issues, Viewpoints, and Voices / Roger Chapman and James Ciment, editors, and a 2016 senior thesis by Yale undergraduate Whitney Wyckoff, "Saved by Chick?: a case study of American Evangelical Christianity, 1960s-1970s," which is available in the Divinity Library's Record Group 95, Reference Collection of Unpublished Papers.
This collection of Chick tracts, compiled by donation and purchase, contains a nearly complete inventory of tracts published by Chick from 1961 to 2015. The tracts are listed in chronological order by their first date of publication. The information about publication date has been taken from a chronological listing of the tracts found at http://www.chickcomics.com. The dates provided would appear to indicate multiple printings of certain tracts over a range of years. The catalog of tracts on the Chick Publications site, http://www.chick.com/catalog/tractlist.asp, has links to online versions of some. In the listing below, an asterisk after the title indicates that the tract is currently out of print and no longer being distributed. The scope and content note indicates whether the art is by Chick himself or by Fred Carter, who was hired by Chick in 1972 to illustrate some of the tracts; this information is as provided by the chickcomics.com website.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
I. Chronological Sequence - 1960s
II. Chronological Sequence - 1970s
III. Chronological Sequence - 1980s
IV. Chronological Sequence - 1990s
V. Chronological Sequence - 2000s
VI. Background Material
Tracts; Chick, Jack T., 1924-2016; Chick Publications
- Chronological Sequence - 1960s, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Titles marked with an asterisk are out of print (as of 2016)
  - Why No Revival?*, 1961,1970,1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Art by Chick
  - A Demon's Nightmare, 1962, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - This Was Your Life!, 1964, 1969, 1972, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Holy Joe, 1964, 1972, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Beast, 1966, 1981, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Somebody Goofed, 1966,1969,1972,2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Creator or Liar?, 1969, 1972, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Who, Me?*, 1969,1973,1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Combined art by Chick, 4 copies including versions 0530.1,0829.7
  - Somebody Loves Me, 1969,1972,1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Art by Chic, 2 copies
- Chronological Sequence - 1970s, Series II
  - Bewitched?, 1970,1972,2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Big Daddy?, 1970,1972,1992,2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - What's Your Score? *, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Lost Continent *, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Art by Chick, A JTCMFA discovery from 2006
  - Escape, AKA The Great Escape, 1971,1972,1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Poor Revolutionist, 1971, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Thing *, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Wordless Gospel, New Guinea, 1971,1972,1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Assignment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Fool!, 1972,1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Frame Up *, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Art by Carter
  - The Gay Blade *, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - One Way!/ True Path, 1972,2002/2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Passover Plot?, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Secret of Prayer*, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Last Generation, 1972,1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Wordless Gospel, Haitian *, 1973,1975,1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Redrawn Wordless Gospel (#19) for Haitains by Carter
  - Room 310, 1973,2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Missionaries are Fools *, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kings of the East*, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Mad Machine, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hi There!, 1975,2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Humbug!, 1975,1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The Contract!, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Happy Hour, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Support Your Local Jew*, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A Love Story, 1977,2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Soul Story*, 1977,2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Sissy?, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - How to Get Rich (And Keep It), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Hit Parade*, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Chronological Sequence - 1980s, Series III
  - That Crazy Guy!, 1980,1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - My Name?... In the Vatican?, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Are Roman Catholics Good Christians?, 1981,1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Kiss The Protestants Good- Bye*, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Big Spender*, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Back from the Dead?, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reverend Wonderful, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Art by Carter, 2 Copies
  - The Letter, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Is There Another Christ?, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Art By Chick
  - The Poor Pope?*, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Wounded Children*, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Titanic, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Dark Dungeons, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bad Bob!, 1983,1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The Word Became Flesh, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ivan the Terrible*, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Holocaust*, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lisa*, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Visitors, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Crisis, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Only Hope, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Story Teller*, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The First Jaws*, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Attack, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Art by Chick, 2 Copies
  - Fire Starter?*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Angels?*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Bull*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Satan's Master*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Trick*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Who Are they Gonna Remember?, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Hunter*, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Terminator?*, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Miss Universe, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Four Brothers/ renamed later as Four Angels*, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Why is Mary Crying?, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Poor Little Witch*, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Greatest Story Ever Told, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Death Cookie, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - The Trap*, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Doom Town, 1989,1991,1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Art by third artist and Carter
  - Fat Cats, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Tiny Shoes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - That Old Devil*, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Wicked Magistrate*, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Art by Carter. Korean version
- Chronological Sequence - 1990s, Series IV
  - The Warning, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Empty Tomb, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Art by Third artist and Carter
  - The Deceived*, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Royal Affair, 1990,1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Art by third artist and Cater
  - Superman?*, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - The Traitor, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Earthman, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Burn Baby Burn*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Killer Storm, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Outsider*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Dreamer*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Sacrifice*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Boo!, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Going Home*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Art by Carter 1991
  - The Scoundrel*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Plagues*, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sin Busters, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Going to the dogs*, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Execution, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Brat*, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - He Never Told Us!, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Thief, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Present, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Hit*, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Tycoon, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Long Trip, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Art by Chick. Two copies of 0423.1
  - Allah Had No Son, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Trust Me!, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Last Rites, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ransom*, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baby Talk, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cleo, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Where's Rabbi Waxman?*, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Trial, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Happy Halloween, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Gomez is Coming, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Best Friend, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Gun Slinger, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Charlie's Ants, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Art by Chick. Two copies including versions 0813.13 and 0416.1
  - No Fear?, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Picture Gospel, African*, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Redrawn version of Wordless Gospel for Africans by Chick
  - The Little Princess, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Flight 144, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Party Girl, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Slugger, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Love the Jewish People, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Retitled version of Support Your Local Jew and Jeopardy
  - The Accident, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Choice, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Art by Chick. Two copies, including 0509.1 and 0706.12
  - The Secret*, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Great One, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Superstar, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Redrawn version of The Slugger for soccer fans by Chick
  - Murph, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - The Pilgrimage*, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - War Zone, 1999,2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The True Path, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Redrawn Native American version of One Way by Chick
- Chronological Sequence - 2000s, Series V
  - Who Murdered Clarice?, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - In the Beginning, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - It's Coming!, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sin City, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Promise, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Art by Chick. Two copies of version 0418.1
  - The Little Ghost, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Big Deal*, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Art by Chick. This was originally thought to be Chick's 150th tract, until two lost tracts were discovered, making The Promise Chick's 150th tract.
  - Framed*, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - It's the Law, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Outcast, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Scam, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Loser, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Last Judge, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Art by Chick. Two copies including 1207.15, 0215.2
  - The Nervous Witch, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Caught!, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Payback!, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Real Heat*, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Monster*, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Gladys*, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - God With Us*, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Fallen*, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Who Cares?, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Scream!, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Good Ol' Boys*, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Man In Black*, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Who's Missing?*, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Here he Comes*, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Busted!*, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - You Are About To See...*, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Are by Chick
  - The Sky Lighter, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Li'l Susy, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Apes, Lies, and Ms. Henn*, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Birds and The Bees*, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Unloved, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Peace Maker, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Devil's Night, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Squatters, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Little Bride*, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Kidnapped!*, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Something in Common?, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Wall, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - What's Wrong With This?*, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Missing Day, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Dirty Diamond*, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Chaplain*, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Four Angels?, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Art by Chick. Retitled version of Four Brothers
  - It's Your Life!, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Redrawn African American version of "This is Your Life" by Carter
  - The Star*, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Congratulations!*, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Who is Allah?*, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Redrawn African American version of "Allah Had No Son" by Carter
  - Men of Peace?, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Here, Kitty Kitty!, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Soul Sisters, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Redrawn African American version of "Allah Had No Son"
  - The Unwelcome Guest*, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Who Loves You?, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Redrawn African American version of "A Love Story" by Carter
  - Heart Trouble, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Set Free!, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fame, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Redrawn African American version of "The Star" by Carter
  - Free at Last!*, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Redrawn African American version of "Set Free!" by Carter
  - Guilty?*, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - There Go The Dinosaurs!*, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Where Did They Go?*, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Unforgiven?, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Poor Little Lamb*, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fatal Decision, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Oops!, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Redrawn African American version of "Somebody Goofed" by Carter
  - Moving On Up*, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Who is He?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - First Bite, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Somebody Angry?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Home Alone?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Art by Chick. originally only in the Hot Topics Book, but later as tract.
  - Papa?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - It's All About You!, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Evil Eyes, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - It's a Deal, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Bully, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Some Like It Hot, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - It's Not Your Fault, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Art by Chick, released Halloween eve 2009
  - No Liars in Heaven, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Art by Chick, promo tract for "Look What's Missing" book. Three copies: 0103.13, 0928.15,0227.13
  - Crazy Wolf, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Going Down?, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Is Allah Like You?, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - The Little Sneak, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Things to Come?, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Stinky, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Love That Money!, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Uninvited, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - You Have a Date!, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Female version of "This Was Your Life."
  - Still No Revival?, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    A sequel to Why No Revival, but all new art and story by Chick
  - That's Baphomet?, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Revised version of Curse of Baphomet. Same art by Chick, but a few different photos and info.
  - Mean Mama, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Walking Dead?, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Awful Truth, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Your Big Moment, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Black Woman's Version of "This Was Your Life." Art by Carter.
  - Here Comes the Judge, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Global Warming, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Why Should I?, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Wassup?, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Black cast version of "Hi There" with art by Carter
  - Camel's In The Tent, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Born Wild!*, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Satan Comes to Salem, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Art by Chick. Three copies of 1017.12
  - Who's The Real Hater?, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Art by Chick. Two versions 0225.13 and 0727.15
  - Mama's Girls, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Let's Fly Away, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sorry, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Art by Chick. "Reverend Wonderful" re-released
  - Cathy, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Art by Chick. "Four Angerls" re-released
  - The Last Surprise, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Art by Chick, Squatters rereleased
  - Spooky, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Art by Chick. Dark Dungeons re-released.
  - Twin Towers, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Art by Chick (Earthman re-released)
  - War Games!, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Art by Chick (Plus a Muslim Version of TWYL (Your Best Life) issued).
  - Your Best Life, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Muslim Version of TWYL with art by Carter
  - It's Who You Know, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Art by Chick. 9Killer Storm Reissued)
  - Just One More, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Art by Chick.
  - The Only Way, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    African American version of "One Way" with art by Carter
  - What's Worse?, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Throw Away Kid, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kura's Ants (Box 4, Folder 3)
    African American version of "Charlie's Ants" with art by Carter
  - Mary's Kids, 2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Where's your Name?, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Man of the Match, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    African American version of "Superstar" with art by Carter
  - Bed Time, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Greatest Insult, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sneakers, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    African American version of "Tiny Shoes" with art by Carter
  - And it Was Good!, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rotten Rodney, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Holy Night, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Keep The Secret, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Background Material, Series VI
  - Website printouts of tract titles (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 5 issues of Battle Cry, journal published by Chick Publications, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Training booklet - "Who Me?" (Box 4, Folder 7)